open-files-now.com 2015-04-04

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do/do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally indentifiable information you have submitted while on our site. 

We do NOT sell any of your personal data and all information collected is kept confidential.

Cookies - When you visit our websites, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of the user experience. We never use cookies to store and send personal information.

We take security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

#### 

Unable to open a certain file?

Try using FilesOpened which comes with ImproveSpeedPC - FilesOpened contains a list of file formats & the types of software which can be used to open these extensions.

System Requirements:

  * Windows XP
  * Windows® Vista
  * Windows 2000
  * Windows 7

Download this software by clicking on the "Download Now" link, or [clicking here](http://improvespeedpc.s3.amazonaws.com/ImproveSpeedPC.exe).

#### Are you tired of having a slow computer? 

#### ImproveSpeedPC is the solution to your computer troubles 

  * ImproveSpeedPC allows you to choose which programs load during Windows Startup so you save time during the Windows Startup. 
  * ImproveSpeedPC helps you to defragment your Hard Drive, this allows your hard drive to run faster and computer programs take less time to load. 
  * ImproveSpeedPC monitors the list of running processes on your computer so you can choose to terminate any unknown process. 

and much more. 

#### Manage the running processes on your computer

ImproveSpeedPC is able to show you what processes are running on your computer, how much memory and CPU allocation the process is using and it allows you to choose which of these programs to keep running/disable.

#### Manage your Windows Startup Items

To ensure that your computer does not take too long to load into Windows, you should manage your Windows Startup items and ensure you're loading the minimum number of programs. This will ensure that your computer will load quickly on startup and saves you time. 

#### ImproveSpeedPC offers Technical Support

If you're unable to figure our a certain technical issue, ImproveSpeedPC has a support team who will walk you through step by step , the process on how to solve your current computer problems. 

#### Free Defrag feature 

Your hard drive may also be fragmented after you use it for a long time and this software allows you to defragment your hard drive for free! The benefits of defragmenting your hard drive include your hard drive running faster and programs take less time to load. 

#### Walkthrough on How this software works

The Software System Requirements are Checked

The software ImproveSpeedPC will check your computer hardware to ensure it passes the minimum system requirements. Once your computer system has been verified, the software will begin installation.

Your Computer System is Scanned

The software ImproveSpeedPC does a quick scan of your computer system and you can also access the free features which include Defragment hard drive, modify Windows Startup Items features etc. 

Scan Results are Shown 

Once the scan is complete, this software will make a list of recommendations for you to take. You may choose to fix all these issues or learn more about an specific issue to optimize. Try It Out Now! It has been tested internally by our team and is certified to be virus free. 

#### Awards Won 

Over 100,000 Users have downloaded this software!

**Testimonials**

I was able to use this software to defragment my hard drive and it helped my programs load faster!  
**Grace T.**

ImproveSpeedPC helped me to manage the number of programs which were loading during Windows Startup and it boosted my startup time!  
**Michael S.**
